If I have an application I would like to use them to preview in the editor.
I can use here, like a browser tab or off, so it automatically will search.
But if you don't have it, what I'm going to do, basically, I will use please make it more modern.
It's designed and with big colors animations. After that, please run it, and now, our
is browser. So first, remember that you have to specify a big browser tab is better
because you will open here, and the Google Chrome it will just open as the next video.
But obviously, you have access to the Google Chrome extensions and the sources and tools.
But here, I will just test inside of the cursor application so I will not leave the app that
I set out. So here, it's like an example. I will stop many games simulation, and I can
press enter. So it's updating. When I post the video, I change my load to a composer, so
it will just change. Obviously, you can use the auto. Auto, I think, rely between those
tools and the composer, but you can test it out for yourself and see which one sits you
well. And now, we have an application here. Okay, again, snapshot of current pages.
Let's see. Okay. Let's see if a slick model is designed. And now, obviously, we can do.
We can just try to update. If you don't see it, you can press console P and try to use
the browser, I think. So if I close it, I will just press run, and it's automatically
opening. This is my page, and we'll use a stock game. So this is my app. Looks great. Simple
trading application. We can switch between portfolio and the history. So let's trade this
by maybe like a four stacks of it. I will trade two of it, and one on this. So if I buy
it now, and go to portfolio, we'll see all of it. And we can sell, this is very nice.
I like this slick design application and the history. It works perfectly well. So we have
a possibility to even change between the application. So it's actually great because you
will be able to give some space for users. And it's great. So we have a stock. We can adjust
the design for it. So if you want to like change some of it like a total volume profit,
you can change the colors of history. And what's that really like? Because they add like
a select element feature. So you can select an enemy tab, for example, and allow people
to make it. So I would just select any element. We can select like diff, or tech trading
game, or maybe I want to remove it, something, or add a new button, especially. So we'll
be able to change it. First, I will change this. And as you can see, I have adjustment
in the browser, and I have adjustment for this specific panel. Now when I have selected
element, please remove this element, and merge it into one stock market place, and allow
us to switch between profiting, analyzing stacks. And we do automatic change. So remove
the header, and it will add some possibility to change. I will leave this application as
this. And then switch between, oh, it's very fast. We already see some of this profiting
and logic. It's actually great. It's captured the full page. So see the chat context summarized.
We might run off of the context used. So if you are running off, it's great to use a
new agent. And then try to implement new agent for a new feature. Otherwise, it can start
to hallucinate and make it a little bit buggy. So it's not testing. So we see even the test life there.
So it again, it captured the full page. Give that your mind. You can also review all of
the changes that the agent has implemented. So it will just try to look to plan for the
next moves. Okay, let me see. I can change myself as you can see. Oh, I love this animations.
I love everything. So this way we can actually use from the mark. Obviously portfolio has
the same. We are losing everything. But for the market, we can just profit. So maybe if you
want to have like some sort of simulation and possibility. I think I don't need it because
I already reached a 100% context use. So we open a new agent and when you open a new agent,
we can try to apply a new changes. And if you have it in a browser, keep that in mind
obviously, you can select any element a game and just point it here. And because it's
a new agent, we'll be able to make it, for example, now I want to maybe I will add like
a new bar to change the language. So views add here and language toolbar to switch between
English and Chinese. The context is no longer fully added and I add a new feature. I will
run a game. And yeah, we can always resolve or run it. All right. And as you see, it has
been added. So we have an option. We switch and we have the name. We can obviously add
a new localized, but still there is a bottom. And this agent can be obviously for us to
maybe make like change not at language, but localization agent. And this way we can try to
manage and adjust for our purposes. It's pretty great. And the only thing I don't like
that if you have an element, our microphone feature is disappearing. So if you want to just
add like a normal one, average. Obviously, and if you have like our translation, because
it's a drug down, so I see like the Chinese and our microphone I can hear is disappearing.
So this time we can try to voice input. So I'll use it for now. I would like to implement
Chinese translation in the content as well, because on the tab bar is translated. It
will expand the translation. We see the list of to do actually for the translation we could
start from the plan as well. I think it's a great to start a new agent for a new feature
and start from the plan and then slow implement. And it's a great habit. So it will implement
and add like Chinese JSON file with a translation. So we try to add local wise things. All
the causation agent has finished. So we can now try it out. If I type now Chinese, I think
everything has been translated except obviously in the name of the companies, but it's obvious
and we can very nice, quickly change our application. It's great. So running in a well
application, but we can try other different frameworks, but we see the potential of course
or how we create more useful application. At last, but not least, if you have problems
with running a web browser inside of the cursor. So what you can do, you can run and
publish as a administrator, use this comment, set execution policy, remote sign it, please
remember to copy it, and then press yes to all, which is a key. It will allow you to execute
external scripts that are required in order to use some other functionality that I've tested
in this video.